<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>dylan on - Longform Posts</title>
		<description>Posts categorized as 'longform'</description>
		<link>https://dylanon.com</link>
		<atom:link href="https://dylanon.com/feed.longform.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #6</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;I ordered lunch through an app. I don’t usually order lunch, but today I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I walked into the restaurant and I saw a bag with my name on it so I grabbed it. 
I said a quick thank you, but too quiet and to no one in particular so no one looked up. Then I left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m thinking about the ways the Internet makes my body invisible in the real world in the name of efficiency, 
and how in my brain there’s many reasons why I should be concerned about this. But in how I feel, I guess I don’t really mind.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 12:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-6/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-6/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #5</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Did you watch the Tonys?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s thought is about the art we love and what happens, or how it feels, when we stop loving it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These days I sit through a musical the same way I think Kevin Spacey does – with a polite smile that doesn’t reach my eyes.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:59:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-5/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-5/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #4</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, it’s Dylan again. Thought #4 is about sharing, artistic labour, and money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be among the first to advocate for more openness, more sharing of artistic works, the ability to build upon them… I think that if art is a public good it should be freely available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I have to wonder if sharing freely in this way undervalues - devalues artistic labour in an industry that already has problems being undervalued socially and with actual dollars.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 10:27:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-4/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-4/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #3</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, it’s Dylan with Thought #3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As scrappy as theatres can be, we use a lot of technology, and most of it is proprietary. Other people build it, and theatres pay to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been dreaming of a world where theatres will have the money to hire technical people to be on staff to collectively build and maintain the 
tools we need as an industry, and make them freely available for anyone’s use. So, that’s the idea - Let’s do it! I don’t know where we find the money, 
but let’s open source theatre technology.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 11:43:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-3/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-3/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #2</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, it’s Dylan and this is my second thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m thinking about &lt;a href=&quot;http://semver.org/&quot;&gt;Semantic Versioning&lt;/a&gt;, so for example, the process that governs our move from version 1 to version 2. In software, this is a huge shift introducing backwards-incompatible changes that mean you can’t use that software in the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can re-invent &lt;em&gt;Romeo &amp;amp; Juliet&lt;/em&gt; into version 2 and demand a fundamentally different engagement with that work, but the important question is: How do we get to version 3 from there, and how far can we go?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 13:09:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-2/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-2/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>SpiderWebShow Thought Residency - #1</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is Dylan On.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I’m thinking about artistic and cultural institutions and their subjectivity. Namely - do they have one?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can institutions exist in a real way where they can bear responsibility, or do individuals like me simply speak them into existence?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess what I’m wrestling with is:
When institutions fail… does the buck stop with me?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 10:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-1/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/spiderwebshow-thought-residency-1/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>A Few Quick Highlights from PACTcon</title>
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Feeling rejuvenated and charged with purpose and possibility after attending (and staffing) the &lt;a href=&quot;https://conference.pact.ca/&quot;&gt;PACT conference&lt;/a&gt; last week. Cannot believe how many artistic people I met! So lucky. Feeling like I have a much better idea of the organization’s place (and my place) in the sector, and some new ideas about approaches I can take to my work.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 16:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
				<link>https://dylanon.com/pactcon2017-highlights/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://dylanon.com/pactcon2017-highlights/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
